jobs4jobs.com 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Jobs4jobs.com

**W** e at Jobs4jobs.com - online job board understand your need to maintain your privacy when searching for a job. Jobs4jobs.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We want to provide a safe, secure user experience. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us is used only for the purposes as set forth herein.

• Aggregated Data about Jobs4jobs.com Visitors

We gather information about all of our users collectively, such as what area users visit most frequently. We only use such data anonymously and in the aggregate. This information helps us to determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall experience for you. We may share this information with third parties, but only in the aggregate, so that they too may understand how Jobs4jobs.com visitors use our site, so they may create a better overall experience for you as well.

• Personally Identifiable Information

Jobs4jobs.com - online job board collects personally identifiable information from users when you register for an account, when you use certain products or services and when you enter promotions or contests. We may also ask you for other information, such as information on your interests, your likes and dislikes regarding the site, the types of jobs you are interested in, etc., in an effort to deliver to you the best possible site experience.

• Internet Protocol Address

We collect an IP address from all visitors to our site. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you when you visit our site.

• General Information Disclosure

Except as described in this privacy policy, we do not disclose your personal information including your individual visits to our Web site, or personal information that you provide, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, personal references, etc., to any outside parties, except when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with law, enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or protect the rights, property or safety of Jobs4jobs.com, our users, or others. But, we may record and share aggregated information with our partners, member companies and job seekers. Also, if you input your information on a co-branded page, then your information becomes the property of both Jobs4jobs.com and the co-sponsor of the page. In that instance, the use of your personal information by our partner company will be subject to the privacy policy of that company and Jobs4jobs.com is not responsible for their use of your personal information.

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our web servers, analyzing data, processing credit card payments, and providing marketing assistance and customer service. These other companies may have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any third party.

• Resumes

Since Jobs4jobs.com - is a online job board, we give you the option of putting your resume in our database, to be searched by prospective employers / recruiters or responding to individual ads with your resume. If you allow your resume to be searchable, then all recruiters who access to our resume database product will have access to your resume. We use our best efforts to grant access to this database only to recruiters, hiring managers, headhunters, and human resource professionals. However, we are not responsible if some other third party, such as someone posing as the aforementioned and evades security measures and gains access to the database, and, subsequently, your resume. You may remove your resume from our searchable database at any time. However, recruiters who have access to the database may have retained a copy of your resume in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of resumes in these instances.

• Updating Account Information

Jobs4jobs.com allows you to change, correct or remove your personal information at any time. To do so, simply log into your Jobs4jobs member area and you will find options for editing the information you have submitted.

• Public Forums

Our Web Site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

• Electronic Newsletters

Jobs4jobs emails a free informational electronic newsletter to only subscribed users. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by utilizing the unsubscribe options at the end of each mailing.

• Tell A Friend

Users can choose to electronically notify Jobs4jobs of an individual who may be interested in our services. Users must provide Jobs4jobs with the email address of the intended recipient. This information is not retained nor used for any other purpose than the intent of promoting our services to that individual one time.

• About Cookies

Cookies, which are small text files recorded in a user's hard drive, are employed by thousands of sites to enhance user's Web viewing experience. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read information from a user's hard drive. Cookies allow Web sites to "remember" users across pages of a Web site and across multiple visits to a Web site. We use cookies for remembering preferences, maintaining information about whether you're currently logged into our systems, and tracking click streams. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, consistent, updated results, and a more personalized site experience. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. In the course of serving advertisements to our Web site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a Web site's functionality if you do so. 

• Banner Advertising

Jobs4jobs.com uses a third party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our Web site. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our Web Site and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on our Web Site and other Web sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Jobs4jobs.com also shares Web site usage information about visitors to our Web site with a reputable third party for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on our Web Site and other Web sites. To do this, we use clear GIF, or pixel tags, on our Web Site, which allow us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits our Web Site. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable.

• Feedback

Jobs4jobs.com has an area on the site where you can submit feedback. Any feedback that is submitted through this area becomes the property of Jobs4jobs.com. We may use this feedback, such as success stories, for marketing purposes, or to contact you for further feedback on the site.

• Privacy Commitment Changes

If we decide to change our privacy commitment for Jobs4jobs.com, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Users will be notified of any changes to Jobs4jobs's privacy policy statement via our electronic mailings and a notice posting on our home page. If any changes apply to the use of personally identifiable information, we will notify the user by email.

• Avoid scams and fraud

Don’t pay a fee upfront! Most legitimate employment agencies don’t charge unless they actually succeed in getting you a job, and often it’s the new employer who pays. Beware any deal involving Western Union, Moneygram, wire transfer, cashier check, money order, shipping, escrow, or any promise of transaction protection / certification / guarantee

Last updated, 12/01/2014
